All the stuff we couldn't pack into number two.
Jackass 2.5 is a comedy, documentary film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
The crew have now set off to finish what as left over from Jackass 2.0, and in this version they have Wee Man use a 'pee' gun on themselves, having a mini motor bike fracas
in the grocery mall, a sperm test, a portly crew member disguised as King Kong, as well as include three episodes of their hilarious adventures in India.
Self, played by Johnny Knoxville.
Self, played by Steve-O.
Self, played by Bam Margera.
Self, played by Chris Pontius.
Self, played by Spike Jonze.
Self, played by Jeff Tremaine.
Jackass Forever (stylized as jackass fore♥er) is a 2022 American reality slapstick comedy film directed and produced by
Jeff Tremaine, along with producers Spike Jonze and Johnny Knoxville, and was released by Paramount Pictures.
It is the fourth main installment in the Jackass film
series, following Jackass 3D (2010).
The film stars original Jackass members Knoxville, Steve-O, Dave England, Wee Man, Danger Ehren, Chris Pontius, Preston Lacy, as well as newcomers
Sean "Poopies" McInerney, Zach Holmes, Jasper Dolphin, Eric Manaka, Rachel Wolfson, the Jackass film crew, and celebrity guests.
This is the first Jackass film not to feature Ryan Dunn following his death in 2011, and the first without Bam
Margera being a primary cast member as he was fired during production, appearing in only one skit.
Jackass Forever premiered at the Chinese Theatre in Hollywood, California, on
February 1, 2022, and was theatrically released on February 4.
The film was well-received by critics, with many
considering it the best film of the franchise.
It was also a commercial success, grossing over $80 million
worldwide against a budget of $10 million.
Unused footage from the film was compiled separately, titled
Jackass 4.5, and released on Netflix on May 20, 2022.
A sequel is set to release on June 26, 2026.
The film explores themes of pain, disgust, stunt, stuntman, stupidity.
The tone is lighthearted.